(Leonard:)Okay.
(Leonard:)Speaking of what the heart wants, um...
(Leonard:)...a long time ago I made a pact
with Wolowitz that kind of involves you.
(Penny:)Okay, I don't know
where you're going with this...
(Penny:)...but tread carefully because it may be
the last conversation we ever have.
(Leonard:)No, no, nothing like that.
No, the deal was that
if either of us ever got a girlfriend...
(Leonard:)...we'd have her fix the other one up
with one of her friends.
(Penny:)You thought a good time to bring this up
would be right after sex?
Well, I sure as hell wasn't gonna
bring it up before sex.
(Leonard:)And during I was trying to remember
what I read on Google, so....
(Penny:)I'm not hooking Wolowitz up
with my friends.
(Howard:)Come on,
it doesn't have to be a good friend.